It's an incredible experience.
It even changed my life a little.
My name is Juliana, I'm Colombian.
I arrived in August 2025.
I started at A2, now I'm at C1.
I wanted to study here, in France,
to continue my studies here.
So I decided to learn French.
And I found it's easier
and more efficient to do it in France.
We have lots of chances to practice.
Not only in class,
but at the supermarket, at restaurants…
All the teachers are really nice,
and they help us.
It's great, because we always feel
supported, not alone in this experience.
When we played board games,
we really laughed, we had so much fun.
And at the same time, we were learning…
I think it was direct and indirect objects.
It's really fun, we laugh a lot,
but we also learn a lot.
I went to a wine cellar in Lyon,
to eat cheese and drink wine.
It was really interesting,
we learned the whole process.
It's amazing to see things face to face,
not just online, in a picture.
I like Lyon because it's calm,
but there's a lot to do:
museums, restaurants…
So it's really great.
It's an incredible experience.
It even changed my life a little.
So I recommend it, you'll see!